Alexander Makaryk

Android Developer/Software Engineer

Levittown, PA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Alexander-Makaryk/3ff0a4e05e801824

I am a focused and dedicated individual with a diverse skillset and years of experience in software engineering as well as customer service and project management. I am strong willed and always strive to maintain an efficient working environment. I endeavor to anticipate operational problems and swiftly move to mitigate any forthcoming issues.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Android Developer/Software Engineer

Kelly Services - 2014 to November 2015

2014 - Nov 2015

- Quickly adapted to ever changing working environments and rapidly developed efficient solutions to operational challenges.
- Android Developer/Software Engineer Dec

Independent Contractor

Gray Street Solutions - 2013 to November 2014

Consulted on Mobile Application design and initiated exploratory research into efficient solutions to platform challenges.

 Provided direct Client interaction to assist with App planning and design process as well as provide technical support for Google Play and other 3rd party services.

Sales Associate / Keyholder

Self Employed - 2011 to December 2013

2011 - Dec 2013

- Managed personal time and computing resources so as to build an intimate familiarity with the nuances of Android App development.
- 3. Sales Associate / Keyholder

: ov

Aug

Ν

Radioshack - 2009 to August 2011

Nov 2011 - Jan 2012

- Proactively engaged customers on the sale and service of a large array of products while maintaining a tidy and efficient retail environment.
- Developed and utilized my ability to effectively communicate technical challenges and solutions in the diverse market of consumer electronics.

EDUCATION

Conwell-Egan Highschool - Fairless Hills, PA

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Technical Skills:

Tools and Technologies: Operating Systems & Services: Android SDK, RESTful webservices, Ubuntu Linux (desktop & server), Spring framework, PolymerJS, Android, Windows, Unix, MySQL, NodeJS, Django, BASH scripting. PostgreSQL, Apache Web Server, IPTables, Cron.

Programming Languages:

Java (v5, v6, v7), C# (Mono),:

IDEs and Testing

C/C++, Javascript, Python. Android Studio/IntelliJ, Eclipse,

MonoDevelop, Genymotion, JUnit

Testing.